https://www.ctr4dermatology.com/privacy-policy/

MENU
Dear valued patients,
We are happy to announce our office is fully opened for business. Please note we are still shipping skincare products and order requests can be made via keren@ctr4dermatology.com
For other questions and appointment requests, please call 202 955 5757
For More Info
Be safe!
Dr. Cheryl Burgess & Staff
×
COVID-19 Notice
To All our Patients,
The Center for Dermatology and Dermatologic Surgery is carefully watching the evolution of the COVID-19 outbreak in our area as well as all the Federal Government Safety Recommendations.
In order to guarantee the safety of our staff and patients, changes to our schedule and office hours are being made on very short notice. We understand that this is an inconvenience to many of you, but we are doing our best to keep everyone safe and minimize possible virus spread and transmission.
Arrangements have been made for our office staff to contact anyone who has a scheduled appointment that might be affected by any office closure as soon as the decision is made. We ask you to please check your email, text messages or our Instagram (@ctr4dermatology) and/or website for most updated announcements on office closures or changes in our schedules. If you call our main location at 202-955-5757 during our regular office hours and you receive our office closed message, this means our offices will be closed for the day.
Please remember to follow your state’s COVID-19 protocol if you are experiencing:
Fever
Shortness of breath
Cough
Fatigue
Recent international travel or have been in close contact with someone who has recently travelled abroad
If you have been exposed or think you have been exposed to anyone who has been diagnosed recently with COVID-19
Safety measures implemented at Center for Dermatology and Dermatologic Surgery by Dr. Cheryl Burgess
Please be safe, continue to wash your hands frequently and thoroughly, practice social distancing and pay attention to all health recommendations of your local authorities.
Best Regards,
Cheryl Burgess, MD, FAAD
2311 M Street, NW Suite 504
Washington, DC 20037
202-955-5757
202-955-5797 fax
cheryl.burgess@ctr4dermatology.com
Close
Home
167 Jennifer Rd, Suite W
Annapolis,
MD 21401 | Directions
410.224.1195
Washington
2311 M St. NW, Suite. 504
Washington,
DC 20037 | Directions
202.955.5757
Privacy Policy
Center for Dermatology & Dermatologic Surgery is committed to respecting our visitors’ privacy and protecting their personal information from misuse or unauthorized disclosure and complying with privacy laws.
Center for Dermatology & Dermatologic Surgery values its reputation and aims to maintain high ethical standards in the conduct of our business affairs.
Center for Dermatology & Dermatologic Surgery ("us", "we", or "our") operates www.ctr4dermatology.com (the "Site"). This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site. We use your Personal Information only for providing and improving the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.
What information do we collect?
When filling in forms or calling the phone number listed on the website as appropriate, you may be asked to enter or provide your name, postcode and, email address and telephone number.
We will not collect any information about you without your explicit consent.
We will ask your consent every time we need to collect personal information about you.
We will explain in clear simple terms why we want to collect your information and what we will do with it, before seeking your consent, so you are fully informed. You will be given a clear and unambiguous option to opt in to any communications or services we might want to offer you.
All data is collected directly from you, the individual. We do not collect any of your personal data from any other sources. This includes any publicly accessible lists and or data sources, whether in the public domain or if we have a legitimate interest to be able to access those sources legally.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
Identify you as a user in our system
Provide you with the Services and complete your transactions;
Provide you with customer support;
Help understand your needs and tailor the features and content of the services to you;
Respond to and, as applicable, fulfill your requests, resolve disputes and/or troubleshoot problems;
Send you administrative e-mail notifications, such as security, or support and maintenance advisories;
Send newsletters, surveys, offers, and other promotional materials related to our Services and for other marketing purposes;
Improve the quality and functionality of the services;
Share with our third-party software and services providers in order to facilitate our communications; and
Communicate with you about our services.
Any and all data in respect of – ‘What Information Do We Collect?’ is not subject to any automated decision making. We do not profile you using your data, any actions taken by us or our systems are as a direct result of explicit requests or consents you have chosen.
There are no foreseeable consequences of any significance in respect of providing the data or being removed from the records, except that we will not be able to contact you.
How do we protect your information?
We will store and process your data following industry best practices and security.
We will take all reasonable steps to ensure that there are appropriate arrangements in place that include provisions covering the appropriate secure transfer, handling and processing of the personal information by those entities and third parties.
Do we use cookies?
Yes. Refer our Cookie Policy. Visit:   COOKIE POLICY
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you.  Where processing takes place by one of our trusted data processors, we ensure that our contracts with those third parties contain the appropriate GDPR / PIPEDA
model clauses and that all our third parties are also compliant with the GDPR, PIPEDA this affords your data the same protection away from our organization, as it does within it.
We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Third party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
Your rights as an individual in respect of the data we hold
We respect the rights and freedom of individuals and as such we would like to make you aware of the following.
You have the right to:
Request access to your data
Request rectification of your data where there are errors or inaccuracies, or the data is not current
Request that the data we hold is removed entirely from our systems
Request us to restrict processing your data
Object to our processing your data
Request your data in a format that is commonly used/accepted
Send your data to another controller
Withdraw consent already provided – at any time
You also have the right to complain or withdraw your consent. To exercise your above rights, send a written request to policy@pri-pol.com
Meet Dr. Burgess
Dr. Cheryl M. Burgess is a board-certified dermatologist who has gained national and international acclaim for her expertise and contributions to the field of dermatology. She founded the Center for Dermatology and Dermatologic Surgery in Washington,
Read more about Dr. burgess
Happy Patients Gallery
More Happy Patients
Subscribe to Our Newsletter
By submitting the above form you agree and accept our Privacy Policy
Click Here For Newsletter Archives
Contact Our Washington DC Dermatologist at Center for Dermatology and Dermatologic Surgery Today!
202.955.5757
Scroll
S
5
Shanice E.
"Dr. Burgess is awesome! I would recommend her to anyone. I never write reviews but I was so compelled to write one about how good of an experience I had with her. I have been to several dermatologist before and nobody took as much time as she did to really figure out what was going on with my skin. She took her time, made me feel comfortable, and then gave me a thorough skin care regimen complete with samples! You can immediately pick up on how skilled and experienced she is!"
Originally, Powered By
Read More Success Stories
Home
Meet the Doctor
Contact Us
Privacy Policy
Site Map
Get Social With Us
Washington office: Center for Dermatology and Dermatologic Surgery Located at
2311 M St. NW, Suite. 504, Washington,
DC, 20037 United States
- Phone:
202.955.5757.
Annapolis office: Center for Dermatology and Dermatologic Surgery Located at
167 Jennifer Rd, Suite W, Annapolis,
MD, 21401, United States
- Phone: 410.224.1195.
www.ctr4dermatology.com
© Copyrights 2020 Center for Dermatology & Dermatologic Surgery. All rights reserved. |
Washington :
202.955.5757
Annapolis : 410.224.1195
Washington
Annapolis
Washington :
202.955.5757
Annapolis : 410.224.1195
